India, so I don't really know.
Yeah.
Alright.
Drive with him?
Yeah.
Okay.
But same same price?
Pay this.
But I pay him.
Okay.
Done your batch.
So I'm not sure how this works here now.
Maybe he is like a like a guy, like, contributing to passengers.
And then or maybe he's collecting the commission later from him.
I'm not sure.
If you know how this works here, please feel free to share your knowledge in the comments.
I'm always curious to learn about these things.
So as you can see, the traffic today, at least on this part of the town, is not that bad.
In case you're wondering what time it is, it is early afternoon now.
So I think that this part of Delhi Metro Area is not as busy as the Delhi Center.
So Gurgaon, the town where we're going now, it's basically a satellite city of Delhi.
So I think if you drive from Delhi City Center to this town, should be in total around